http://www.drharveys.com/pages/privacy

0
Fast shipping and 100% satisfaction guaranteed
There are no items in your cart.
Perfect Parrot Food
It looks so incredible you'll want to eat it!
About Dr. Harvey's
Committed to excellence and integrity.
Learn more
×
Privacy Policy
Dr. Harvey’s has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our online information gathering and dissemination practices.
Our overall policy is extremely simple: If we collect information from you, we use it only for the purposes for which it was collected, and the other limited purposes outlined below. We will not sell or share your personally identifiable information with any third party.
Cookies
We may use “cookies” to determine whether you have visited our site previously and to save and remember any preferences that you set while using our site. Our cookies cannot retrieve any other data from a hard drive or obtain an e-mail address. Although a user has the ability to modify most browsers to either accept all cookies, notify the user when a cookie is sent, or reject all cookies, it may not be possible to utilize certain services at Dr. Harvey’s website if cookies are rejected.
Do we use ‘cookies’?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
Keep track of and serve advertisement with a 3rd party.
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
Links
This site contains links to other sites. Dr. Harvey’s is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
While there is no such thing as “perfect” security on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your personally identifiable information. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, we do not assume any liability for third-party usage of your personal information, whether obtained legally or illegally from our system.
Fetch the latest news
Sign up for our newsletter to hear about new products and doggone good deals.
About Dr. Harvey's
Dr. Harvey’s Healthy Formulations makes high quality, safe and natural products for companion animals. We believe your Dogs, Cats and Birds deserve the very best. Our products include complete recipes, base mixes, chemical-free grooming products, and beneficial vitamins and supplements to keep your animal companions healthy and happy.
When you choose Dr. Harvey’s you and your companion animal benefit from 30+ years of research and experience that has made countless pets live long and happy lives. We’re always ready to answer your questions and all of our products are made here in the USA.
Products
Dogs
Cats
Birds
Find A Store
Find a Retail Store
Find an Online Store
Company
